forecasts.org 2002-08-02

# The Financial Forecast Center

### The Financial Forecast Center's Privacy Policy

Applied Reasoning Inc. host of The Financial Forecast Center is committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users. Below is information outlining our continued support for the responsible management of consumer information.

**Data Collection**

The Financial Forecast Center does not use "cookies", a common technique used to collect information about the user.  While this technique can be used to collect or store personal information The Financial Forecast Center does not use this technique and will not collect or store any personal information using cookies or any other techniques.

**Feedback and Contact Forms**

The Financial Forecast Center makes use of feedback and contact forms to allow viewers to contact us.  These forms ask for personal information to allow us to reply to the users if needed.  As stated at the top of each of these forms all information input into these forms are at the discretion of the user and is in no way controlled by The Financial Forecast Center.  All information collected through these forms are used only by Applied Reasoning Inc. host of The Financial Forecast Center.  None of this information is either given nor sold to any third parties.

**Newsletter Subscriptions**

The Financial Forecast Center offers free newsletters to viewers who enter their email addresses.  These addresses are used solely for the purpose of electronic distribution of the stated newsletters and are neither given nor sold to any third parties.

**Internet Web Server Information**

The internet web servers used to distribute the web pages for The Financial Forecast Center collect non-user specific information about when and what web pages are served.  The information collected by the web servers are:  date and time of a web page request, the internet address of the server (not user) requesting the page, the name of the page requested, any errors associated with delivering the web page, and the browser used.  This information is used internally to monitor the popularity of our internet content and to monitor the load on the web servers.  This information does not have any marketing value and is neither given or sold to any third parties.

**Third Party Advertising**

> This site, The Financial Forecast Center, uses the services of Engage Media for the serving and/or targeting of ads, promotions and other marketing messages. To do this Engage collects anonymous data through the use of cookies. To learn more about Engage including your ability to opt out of the Engage system go to <http://www.engage.com/privacy>.
> 
> We also use DoubleClick's Sonar Network and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our web site.  These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visit to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.  If you would like more information abut this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.doubleclick.net/naiprivacy).
> 
> **Third Party Cookies**
> 
> In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.
### The Financial Forecast Center's Privacy Policy

Applied Reasoning Inc. host of The Financial Forecast Center is committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users. Below is information outlining our continued support for the responsible management of consumer information.

**Data Collection**

The Financial Forecast Center does not use "cookies", a common technique used to collect information about the user.  While this technique can be used to collect or store personal information The Financial Forecast Center does not use this technique and will not collect or store any personal information using cookies or any other techniques.

**Feedback and Contact Forms**

The Financial Forecast Center makes use of feedback and contact forms to allow viewers to contact us.  These forms ask for personal information to allow us to reply to the users if needed.  As stated at the top of each of these forms all information input into these forms are at the discretion of the user and is in no way controlled by The Financial Forecast Center.  All information collected through these forms are used only by Applied Reasoning Inc. host of The Financial Forecast Center.  None of this information is either given nor sold to any third parties.

**Newsletter Subscriptions**

The Financial Forecast Center offers free newsletters to viewers who enter their email addresses.  These addresses are used solely for the purpose of electronic distribution of the stated newsletters and are neither given nor sold to any third parties.

**Internet Web Server Information**

The internet web servers used to distribute the web pages for The Financial Forecast Center collect non-user specific information about when and what web pages are served.  The information collected by the web servers are:  date and time of a web page request, the internet address of the server (not user) requesting the page, the name of the page requested, any errors associated with delivering the web page, and the browser used.  This information is used internally to monitor the popularity of our internet content and to monitor the load on the web servers.  This information does not have any marketing value and is neither given or sold to any third parties.

**Third Party Advertising**

> This site, The Financial Forecast Center, uses the services of Engage Media for the serving and/or targeting of ads, promotions and other marketing messages. To do this Engage collects anonymous data through the use of cookies. To learn more about Engage including your ability to opt out of the Engage system go to <http://www.engage.com/privacy>.
> 
> We also use DoubleClick's Sonar Network and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our web site.  These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visit to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.  If you would like more information abut this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.doubleclick.net/naiprivacy).
> 
> **Third Party Cookies**
> 
> In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.
